rockerzindia.com 2014-03-10

# Privacy policy | RockerZ India

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which RZI GROUP collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.RockerZIndia.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by RZI.

Personal identification information:-

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

How we use collected information

RZI may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

\- To personalize user experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

\- To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

### Google Adsense 

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

### Contacting us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: RockerZIndia(RZI)

http://www.RockerZIndia.com/

RockerZIndia Pvt Ltd.

Vijayawada

AndhraPrradesh

chaitu@RockerZIndia.com

This document was last updated on January 25, 2014
